thekewlshop.myshopify.com 2019-12-21

# Security & Privacy | The Kewl Shop

Updated 25 May 2018

This policy sets out how The Kewl Shop uses and protects any information that you give The Kewl Shop when you use this website.

The Kewl Shop is committed to ensuring that your security and privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this statement.

The Kewl Shop may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 19 February 2012.

##### **What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences, and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

##### **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

    * Internal record keeping.
    * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
    * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
    * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

##### **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

##### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.  
We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/thekewlshop.com).  

##### **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

          * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
          * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at us@thekewlshop.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the above address.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

##### 

##### Currency Conversion

By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency.

##### **Display Advertising**

We have implemented and use Google Display Advertising, in particular we use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.

This means a) third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet and b) we and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.

If you prefer you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCg4VHd0m21adYaAg9yNDxJFQTiTSdorWliAwloVbVUTgmchctwp2GJgAjNVdX5eTnvU_liK7Nw1FGvAO2MinLUps2ts4sc__SSyVF7FCU6gglVus727677iacDuZaJDGl9s2vkWKy9gmbFnJTyVHgeNeMVjqG3WCh_5C10Gqr73KbdwD0__6mf5ax3UV_6tHffg9HzX).

For further information we also encourage you look at [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

#####  **Company Details**  

The Kewl Shop Pte. Ltd

Reg #: 201307701C (Singapore)

Reg Address:

51 Goldhill Plaza

#07-10/11

Singapore (308900)
